let savollar25 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "to associate",
        answer: "A. bog'lamoq",
        options: [
            "A. bog'lamoq",
            "B. ajratmoq",
            "C. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "D. adashtirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "environment",
        answer: "B. atrof muhit",
        options: [
            "A. bino",
            "B. atrof muhit",
            "C. ish joyi",
            "D. yer"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "factory",
        answer: "C. zavod",
        options: [
            "A. ofis",
            "B. omborxona",
            "C. zavod",
            "D. ustaxona"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "feature",
        answer: "A. xususiyat",
        options: [
            "A. xususiyat",
            "B. aksessuar",
            "C. qo'shimcha",
            "D. xato"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "instance",
        answer: "D. misol",
        options: [
            "A. hodisa",
            "B. muammo",
            "C. lahza",
            "D. misol"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "to involve",
        answer: "A. jalb etmoq",
        options: [
            "A. jalb etmoq",
            "B. oldini olmoq",
            "C. chiqarib tashlamoq",
            "D. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "medicine",
        answer: "B. dori",
        options: [
            "A. oziq-ovqat",
            "B. dori",
            "C. suv",
            "D. uyqu"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "mix",
        answer: "C. aralashma",
        options: [
            "A. yagona narsa",
            "B. butun",
            "C. aralashma",
            "D. ajratish"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "to organize",
        answer: "A. tashkillashtirmoq",
        options: [
            "A. tashkillashtirmoq",
            "B. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "C. bekor qilmoq",
            "D. buzmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "period",
        answer: "B. davr",
        options: [
            "A. nuqta",
            "B. davr",
            "C. vaqt",
            "D. epoxa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "to populate",
        answer: "C. yashamoq",
        options: [
            "A. yo'q qilmoq",
            "B. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "C. yashamoq",
            "D. bo'shatmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "to produce",
        answer: "A. ishlab chiqarmoq",
        options: [
            "A. ishlab chiqarmoq",
            "B. iste'mol qilmoq",
            "C. yo'q qilmoq",
            "D. saqlamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "range",
        answer: "D. qator",
        options: [
            "A. nuqta",
            "B. chegara",
            "C. birlik",
            "D. qator"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "to recognize",
        answer: "B. tanimoq",
        options: [
            "A. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "B. tanimoq",
            "C. adashtirmoq",
            "D. sezmaslik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "regular",
        answer: "A. muntazam",
        options: [
            "A. muntazam",
            "B. kamdan-kam",
            "C. bir martalik",
            "D. notekis"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "sign",
        answer: "C. belgi",
        options: [
            "A. ramz",
            "B. yo'l ko'rsatkich",
            "C. belgi",
            "D. xarita"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "tip",
        answer: "A. uch",
        options: [
            "A. uch",
            "B. asos",
            "C. yon",
            "D. markaz"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "tradition",
        answer: "B. an'ana",
        options: [
            "A. innovatsiya",
            "B. an'ana",
            "C. o'zgarish",
            "D. uzilish"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "trash",
        answer: "A. axlat",
        options: [
            "A. axlat",
            "B. boylik",
            "C. yaxshi narsa",
            "D. qiymat"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "wide",
        answer: "B. keng",
        options: [
            "A. tor",
            "B. keng",
            "C. qisqa",
            "D. kichik"
        ]
    }
];
